I understand that you see your victory
я так понимаю что ты видишь свою победу
as you having to capture Kyiv Lviv all of
что вы должны захватить Киев Львов всю
Ukraine Yes
Украину Да
Yes half
Да наполовину
Cool Half is like
Прикольно Наполовину- это как
A Kyiv e Kharkov Odessa
А Киев э Харьков Одесса
Yeah So what are you going to do with Kiev
Угу Так что вы будете делать с Киевом
Hello
Здравствуйте
Hello I am from the city of Khmelnitsky Where are you
Здравствуйте Я из города Хмельницкий Вы
from I am
откуда
from the city of St. Petersburg
Я из города Санкт-Петербург
Cool What do you talk about
Прикольно О чём общаетесь
Yes, about everything For example,
Да вообще обо всём Например
how is life how are you doing what are you doing what are you
как жизнь как дела чем занимаетесь что
doing I work as a provocateur
делаете Я работаю провокатором
Provocateur An interesting profession for me I have
Провокатором Интересная для меня
never heard of such a profession I
профессия Никогда такой не слышал
provoke people to think
Провоцирую людей на размышление
Let's try Let's
Давайте попробуем
Cool Why do you think
Да давайте Прикольно Как вы считаете
Russia attacked Ukraine I don't
почему Россия напала на Украину
know I don't think about it
Не знаю не думаю об этом
So let's think I want to provoke you
Так давайте подумаем Я вас хочу
Well, yes, you are a provocateur yes
А ну да вы же провокатор да
Why did Russia attack Ukraine I don't
Почему Россия напала на Украину
know I don't want to Well, options, let's
Не знаю не хочу Ну варианты давайте
try options to think We are people H
попробуем варианты мыслить Мы же люди H
sapience Homo sapiens
sapience человек разумный
Let's options You offer options
Давайте варианты Вы предлагаете варианты
and I choose correctly No no, look,
а я выбираю правильно Нет нет смотрите
it turns out I will impose
это получается я вам буду навязывать
my point of view on you and I, as a competent
свою точку зрения а я как грамотный
provocateur, want to lead you to the point that
провокатор я хочу вас подвести к тому
you yourself give birth to this  point of view
чтобы вы сами родили эту точку зрения
So
Так
Give birth There are
Рожайте
answer options No No No Well,
Варианты ответов есть Нету
what should I
Нету Нету Ну а что мне тогда вам
answer you then You have to come up with the options yourself
отвечать Вы сами должны придумать
Wait a minute
погоди
Yes, at
Да
home, at home
дома дома
I'm at home
Я дома
Yes
Да
So please forgive me for distracting me
Так простите пожалуйста меня отвлекли
Can I ask you again It was mom
Можно ещё раз вопрос Это мама была
Well, roughly speaking,
Ну грубо говоря да В смысле грубо говоря
yes I mean, roughly speaking Well, what difference does it make who it was Well, I'm
Ну вал какая разница кто это был Ну
just wondering who's asking you
просто интересно кто у вас спрашивает
or are you at home demanding that you
или вы дома так требует чтобы вы
answer
ответили
My girlfriend is asking if I'm at home or not Got it
Девушка моя спрашивает дома я или нет
What are the options for why Russia
Понял Какие варианты почему Россия
attacked Ukraine
напала на Украину
Well, Russia attacked Ukraine because because because there
Ну Россия напала на Украину потому
was a war there
что потому что там война была
So there was a war there and that's why Russia
Так там была война и Россия поэтому
attacked Ukraine I don't understand anything No, no,
напала на Украину Ничего не понимаю Нет
no, Russia attacked Why did Russia
ну не не Россия напала Почему Россия
attack Ukraine You had a part of
напала на Украину У вас была часть
Ukraine, there was a part of Ukraine, the
Украины была часть Украины
western part of Ukraine, which wanted to separate
западная вот которая хотела отделиться
from Ukraine, but Ukraine really didn't want that
от Украины а Украина этого очень сильно
And now wait
не хотела И сейчас подождите
Ukraine really doesn't want that, it
Украина очень сильно этого не хотеть
will worry
переживать будет
I'll answer later
Я потом отвечу
I want you to talk normally and not get
Я хочу чтобы ты нормально поговорил не
distracted
отвлекался
Okay, good Hello
Ладно хорошо Алло
Let me come in now Just a
Давай сейчас зайду
second please Okay That's it
Одну секундочку пожалуйста Окей
I'm ready to answer your questions
Всё я готов к ответам на ваши вопросы
So what's there, the Western
Так то что там Западная
Western Ukraine, the western part of Ukraine
Западная Украина западная часть Украины
wanted  to separate from you So but
захотела отделиться от вас Так но
eastern Ukraine really didn't want
восточная Украина очень не хотела
this, so it decided to use force,
этого поэтому ну решила силовым путём
and as for
а а как
taking it away, I can't, eastern
забрать несу восточная
Ukraine Well, formulate your thoughts
Украина Ну формулируй мысли
In short, a piece of eastern
Короче кусок восточной
Ukraine doesn't want to be Ukraine
Украины не хочет быть Украиной
So stop Also Western wanted to separate
Так стоп Тоже Западная хотел отделиться
No Eastern Yes no Lugansk Western Eastern Eastern is
Нет восточная Да нет Луганск Западная
Lviv Bandera No
Львов Бандеры Нет Восточная - это не
Eastern is not Europe Europe is Western And
А восточная - это Азия
eastern is Asia Eastern is Asia Well, also
Восточная - это Азия
part of Europe It's not Asia So then eastern is
Ну тоже часть Европы Это не Азия Так то
also Europe, it turns out Yes Yes So
восточная это тоже Европа получается Да
wait, I'm confused Both Western
Да Так то подожди я запутался И Западная
Europe and Eastern are also Europe And
Европа и Восточная - это тоже Европа А в
what's the problem What's the
чём проблема
problem What's the problem with you
В чём проблема В чём проблема у вас
Wait, why did Russia attack Ukraine
Подожди зачем Россия напала на Украину
You say we had a war And why did
Ты говоришь у нас была война А зачем
Russia attack I don't understand Western
Россия напала Не понял Западная
Eastern You're complicating things I'm saying
восточная что-то усложняешь Я говорю
Eastern Europe
Восточная Европа
part of eastern Ukraine wanted to
часть восточной Украины хотела
separate from Ukraine So And
отделиться от Украины Так
why did you attack
И а зачем вы напали
Well Western Ukraine didn't want
Ну Западная Украина не хотела
more, but a fairly large part of
чтобы больше но достаточно большая часть
eastern Ukraine to separate from Ukraine
Восточной Украины отделилась от Украины
So
Так
and started a war there So why did you
ну и развязала там войну Так а зачем вы
attack Ukraine
напали на Украину
Because these  republics which are in
Потому что эти республики которые в
eastern Ukraine
восточной Украине
they are in short Russia recognized these
они короче Россия признала эти
republics as
республики сам
self-proclaimed and recognized their
самопровозглашёнными и признала их
independence So why did you attack
независимость Так а зачем вы напали на
Ukraine Well then get
Украину
ready to switch in short Okay,
готовишься переключиться короче Ладно
let me get ready later and no come on
давай я потом подготовлюсь и нет давай
Why did you attack Ukraine Don't
Зачем вы напали на Украину Не
switch No no
переключайся
we attacked Ukraine Well why
Да не не на Украину мы напали Ну зачем
Look there is something western and eastern
Смотри там что-то западное и восточное
something in short they had some kind of conflict
что-то короче конфликт какой-то у них
North south central external
был Северная южная центральное внешнее
Yes why did you attack Ukraine and bomb
Да зачем вы напали на Украину и бомбите
You are bombing the cities of eastern Ukraine You are the
Вы бомбите города восточной Украины Вы
city of Bakhmut which in eastern Ukraine you
город Бахмут который в Восточной Украине
destroyed to zero 70,000 of the population The
уничтожили под ноль 70.000 населения
city of Ukraine This is no longer Ukraine
Город Украина Это уже не Украина
right This was eastern Ukraine yes
правильно Это восточная Украина была да
which did not want to be in Ukraine and you
которая не хотела быть в Украине а вы
went and destroyed Ukraine all this is
взяли и уничтожили Украина это всё это
no longer Ukraine yes Why did you destroy the
уже не Украина да Зачем вы уничтожили
city of Bakhmut 70,000 Russian-speaking
город Бахмут Там 70.000 русскоязычного
population of eastern Ukraine lived there
населения восточной Украины жило
This is no longer Ukraine Yes because you
Это уже не Украина Да потому что вы
destroyed this city It does not exist  There's
уничтожили этот город Его нету Там
nothing there A cat should be lying there
ничего нету Там кошка должна лежить
Why did you destroy this city I didn't
Зачем ты уничтожил город этот Я я ничего
destroy anything Well, how did you destroy it Do you support
не уни Ну как уничтожал Ты поддерживаешь
that there are
что
children in Mariupol too
и детки и детей в Мариуполе тоже
Mariupol was a city of half a million Yes
Мариуполь полумиллионный город был Да
Why did you bomb these houses where
Зачем вы разбомбили эти дома где жили
people lived They lived peacefully in Eastern
люди Они спокойно жили в Восточной
Ukraine and the city of Bakhmut People in Eastern
Украине и город Бахмут Люди в восточной
Ukraine lived walked loved Mom
Украине жили ходили любили Мама им
called them That's the thing Are you sure
звонила Дело-то в чём А вы вы уверены
that they wanted to live in Ukraine Look, I'll
что они хотели жить в Украине Я смотри я
explain to you I was born in the city of Donetsk,
а тебе объясню Я родился в городе Донецк
Artem Street 14, apartment 88 This
улица Артёма 14 квартира 88 Уже этого
house is no longer there They tore it down So when
дома нету Снесли его Так вот когда
Russian troops came to
российские войска пришли в четырнадцатом
my native Donetsk in 1914, I'll wait,
году в мой родной Донецк я подождите
can I please give you a preface Come on If
можно пожалуйста предисловие Давай Если
I misunderstand something or
я вот чего-то неправильно понимаю или
explain something incorrectly, maybe
что-то неправильно объясняю может быть
you can explain to me how it
вы мне объясните ну вот как оно есть на
really is I will, I'll be
самом деле Я буду я с удовольствием буду
happy to listen to you Maybe you'll
рад вас послушать Может быть вы ну
say something right Let me
что-то правильное скажете Давай я
explain the right thought I'm explaining So
объясню правильную мысль Объясняю Значит
look Uh  I was born in Donetsk
смотри Ээ я сам родился в городе Донецк
My childhood was spent uh on Artem street the
Моё детство прошло ээ на улице Артёма
central street of Donetsk house 14
центральная улица города Донецка дом 14
apartment 88 My neighbor was Aunt Zoya and I had a
квартира 88 Соседка у меня была тётя Зоя
friend Sanya
друг Саня
Prokhorov from the lesochnitsa playground When
Прохоров Когда в четырнадцатом году
Russian
пришли российские
troops came to Donetsk in 1914 our
войска в Донецк наш
native city was bombed there most often Yes
родной разбомбили там чаще всего Да мы
many of us left Donetsk and moved to the
многие выехали из Донецка и переехали в
city I moved to the city of Bakhmut The city of
город Я переехал в город Бахмут Город
Bakhmut because it was unbearable to live in Donetsk There
Бахмут потому что в Донецке жить было
was lawlessness there Russian
невыносимо Там был беспредел Российские
militants threw everyone into the basement and killed
боевики кидали всех на подвал убивали
My uh neighbor Sanya
Мой ээ сосед Саня
Prokhorov worked in a
Прохоров работал на
mine The mines were
шахте Шахты
closed The only place where you could
закрыли Единственное где можно было
earn extra money was to go stand at checkpoints
подработать - это пойти на блокпостах
and for money with a machine gun He
постоять да за деньги с автоматом Он
went and a mine hit him in the head No Sanya
пошёл прилетела ему мина башку Нет Сани
Prokhorka I couldn't even come to
Прохорка Я даже не смог приехать к
my childhood friend's funeral because
своему другу детства на похороны потому
I won't come either because there is
что и я не приеду потому что там
occupation Yes and yes and there is no friend yes Head,
оккупация Да и да и друга нет да Башку
what is there for him to come well  to look at a friend without
ему что там приехать ну на друга без
looking too it is necessary truth That's all
смотреть тоже оно нужно правда Это всё
But then Russian troops came to the
Но потом российские войска пришли в
city of Bakhmut I lived there for 8 years I lived there No
город Бахмут Я там 8 лет жил 8 лет жил
one spoke Ukrainian there at all you
Там никто по-украински не говорил вообще
understand Everyone there said: teachers
понимаешь Там все говорили: учителя
sellers We were a Russian-speaking city And
продавцы Мы были русскоязычный город И
then we hear that Russia wants to capture the
тут слышим что Россия хочет захватить
city of Bakhmut to free us We also had a
город Бахмут освободить нас У нас ещё
rally with maybe you'll look yeah uh you'll
митинг был с может посмотришь да ээ
find in the news like the residents of Bakhmut are
найдёшь в новостях типа жители Бахмута
against Putin We also spoke out that Putin does
против Путина Мы ещё выступали что Путин
not need to free us There was a rally I was also
не надо нас освобождать Митинг был Я ещё
one of the hosts of the rally We
одним из ведущих митинга
stood with posters and
был Мы с плакатами стояли да иностранным
gave news to foreign journalists that we do not
журналистам давали новости что мы не
want to be freed We
хотим чтобы нас освобождали Мы нормально
live here normally What liberations are you talking about Is
тут живём Какие освобождения Вы
n't it Putin who says: "Yes, let's
что Не Путин говорит: "Да давайте
free Bakhmud because we are being
освободим Бахмуд потому что нас тут
oppressed here" They came and stupidly destroyed our city
ущемляют" Пришли уничтожили наш город
You saw the ruins of Bakhmut You saw what
тупо Ты видел руины Бахмута Видел что с
they did to it
ним сделали
There stupidly everything was destroyed There is not a single
Там тупо под ноль всё Там ни одной
grandmother There is
бабушки нет
not even a single grandmother Grandfather veteran
Даже ни одной бабушки нет Дед ветеран в
lived in the neighboring house Grandfather veteran of the Great
соседнем доме жил Дед ветеран Великой
Patriotic
Отечественной
War 103  my grandfather was 103
войны 103 годаму деду было 103
years old Do you know when he
года Знаешь когда он
died on May 9 during the storming of
погиб 9 мая при штурме
Bakhmut That's it
Бахмута Вот
Okay Wait I get it I get it
это дошёл Ладно Подожди я понял Я понял
Enough What did you get Well no no
Хватит Что ты понял
need for such things No So we need to
Ну не не надо такие вещи Нет Так надо
see who killed this veteran
посмотреть кто убил этого ветерана
Russian
Российская
army Father took Berlin At least that's what he
армия Отец Берлин брал По крайней мере
told us neighbors He
так нам рассказывал соседям Медали
showed us medals Well okay Why Okay The
показывал Ну ладно Зачем Хорошо
next question is completely independent
Следующий вопрос вообще независимый
Why are you telling me this
Зачем вы мне это говорите
Well you asked me to I am an ordinary citizen of
Ну ты же попросил чтобы Я обычный житель
Russia I am not a serviceman I am there uh well I don't
России Я не не военнослужащий Я там ээ
do anything like that Why are you
ну ничем подобным не занимаюсь Вот вы
asking me such questions Why are you
зачем мне такие вопросы задаёте Зачем вы
specifically presenting this to me
именно конкретно мне это предъявляете
What should I do
Что я должен сделать
Well look I warned you that I am a
Ну смотри я же тебе предупреждал что я
provocateur a professional
провокатор профессиональный
provocateur I provoke people to
провокатор Я провоцирую людей на
think It seems to me that I
мышление Мне кажется что немножко
managed to work with you a little bit really
удалось с тобой поработать правда
Maybe maybe That is to say
Может быть может быть То есть у тебя
your inner Google turned on you
включился твой внутренний Google ты
started asking yourself questions and you felt
начал себе задавать вопросы и тебе стало
heavy from these questions Wait I am taking into
тяжело от этих вопросов Подождите я
account I am also taking into account the fact that you
учитываю я учитываю ещё тот факт что вы
may be telling me a lie Let's
может быть говорите мне неправду Давайте
check Look at the photos of the
проверим Посмотри фотографии
destroyed Bakhmut is this true or
разрушенного Бахмута правда это или
not true
неправда
Well, about the destroyed Bakhmut, I know for sure
Ну про разрушенный Бахмут я знаю точно
that it was completely destroyed, the whole city Yes,
что он полностью разрушен весь город Да
I know that Yes
это я знаю Да
So who destroyed it Specifically, specifically,
Так кто его разрушил Конкретно конкретно
Personally, what did I do to you that was bad
Лично я что я вам сделал плохого
You specifically didnt do anything good
Ты конкретно ничего не сделал хорошего
So what about the people you chat with in chat roulette
Так а с людьми которыми в чат-рулетке
that you come across, what did he do to you that was
общайтесь которые вам попадается что он
good I dont
вам сделал хорошего
know what, lets do it this way What can a person
Не знаю что давай так Что человек может
do that was good for Ukraine
сделать хорошего для Украины
For Ukraine Yeah, what specifically Question
Для Украины Угу Что конкретно Вопрос ещё
again I didnt get it
раз Я не понял
Lets do it this way Whats simple Ill provoke
Давай так Что простое Я так спровоцирую
you to think Whats simple, a good
тебя на мышление Что простой хороший
Russian Thats how you can do that was
русский Вот как ты может сделать
good for Ukraine
хорошего для Украины
I dont know what, make it difficult to go Well, for
Я не знаю что затрудняйся идти Ну
example, send some kind of donation to ZSU They
например отправить на ЗСУ какой-то донат
definitely wont send any donations to ZSU from Russians
ЗСУ из русских точно донат никакой не
Why Well,
отварят Почему
because good Russians send
Ну потому что хорошие русские отправляют
No, they dont send They send Yes,
Нет не отправляют Отправляют
seriously, show the translations Why
Да серьёзно Покажите переводы Зачем
show off people They send
показывать светить людей Отправляют
No, they dont send There are still good
Нет не отправляют Есть ещё хорошие
Russians who are there, well, all sorts of
русские которые там ну всякие
transformer booths, watching
трансформаторные будки смотрят
railroad
железнодорожные
crossings You understand me
переезды Ты меня понял
These are good Russians, yes Yes, these are good
Это хорошие русские да Да это хорошие
Russians They are bringing the end of this regime closer
русские Вот приближают кончину этого
These are bad ones  Russian
Это нехорошие русские
Why Let me provoke you some more How do
Почему Давай ещё попровоцирую тебя Как
you think how much Russia should kill its own
ты считаешь сколько Россия должна убить
people and Ukrainians so that you would say
своих людей и украинских чтобы ты сказал
that this needs to be stopped
что это надо останавливать
And how many should Ukraine kill its own
А сколько Украина должна убить своих
people so that this So We are defending Look,
людей чтобы это Так Мы защищаем Смотри
we are defending our territory You came to
мы защищаем свою территорию Вы пришли на
our territory Tell me I understand I
нашу территорию Вот скажи Я понял я
understand
понял
How much How much should Ukraine kill its
Сколько Сколько Украина должна убить
own people to defend its
своих людей чтобы защитить свою
territory Ukraine does not kill its own
территорию Украина не убивает своих
people Ukraine kills Russian
людей Украина убивает российских
occupiers In order to defend its
оккупантов Для того чтобы защитить свою
territory, all Russian occupiers need to be killed The
территорию нужно убить всех российских
formula is simple here, yes Now
оккупантов Тут формула проста да Теперь
the question That's why you are sitting somewhere
вопрос Вот вы поэтому ты сидишь где-то
Look, you came, you came to Ukraine, yes
смотри вы пришли вы пришли в Украину да
You came to Ukraine, yes You kill your own
Вы пришли в Украину да Убиваете своих
people, you kill a huge
людей убиваете украинцев огромное
number of Ukrainians on both sides
количество и с той и с другой стороны
Because you came with a war to
Из-за того что вы пришли войной чтобы
stop this, you just need to leave and that's it
это остановить вам просто уйти надо и
Stop the war like you
всё Остановить войну как из Афганистана
left Afghanistan So here's the question: how many
вышли Так вот вопрос: сколько для тебя
Russians will be killed for you personally A million 2
лично будет погибших россиян Миллион 2
million three so that you can say: "Well, we don't need
млн три чтобы ты сказал: "Ну не нужна
this war" How many
эта война" Сколько
Listen, well, I have the same question for you
Слушай ну вот у меня для тебя такой же
How many Ukrainians will be killed
вопрос Сколько будет погибших украинцев
I'll explain I'll explain Look  Ukraine
Объясняю объясняю Смотри Украина не
cannot stop because if
может остановиться потому что если у
Ukraine has nowhere to retreat Russia came to
Украине некуда отходить Россия пришла в
Ukraine it simply to start a war it
Украину ей просто становить войну она
look look Russia simply takes and
смотри смотри Россия просто берёт и
leaves the border of Ukraine and that's it and the war
уходит за границу Украины и всё и война
stops Ukraine has nowhere to go
останавливается Украине некуда уйти
Ukraine is on its own territory If for
Украина на своей территории Если б мы
example we and Russia clashed somewhere
например мы и Россия где-то столкнулись
in Belarus yes we are there well come on you
в Белоруссии да мы там а ну давайте вы
retreat or we retreat Yes here we could
отойдите или мы отойдём Да тут можно
discuss Ukraine is on its own
было бы обсуждать Украина на своей
territory where it should
территории куда она должна
retreat How do you see it
отойти Как ты это видишь
Question again Well look and as I see it
Вопрос ещё раз Ну смотри и как я вижу
in order for the war to stop Russia should
чтоб остановилась война Россия должна
leave Ukraine for its own territory
уйти из Украины на свою территорию
Ukraine cannot leave because Ukraine is already on its own
Украина не может уйти потому что Украина
territory Where
и так на своей территории Куда она
should it go Ukraine In your opinion
должна уйти Украина По-твоему
it should not go anywhere It will simply
Никуда она не должна уйти У неё просто
run out of troops and that's it Yes Yes Look
закончится войска и всё Так Так Смотри
if Ukraine runs out of troops then
если в Украине закончатся войска тогда
you will seize all of Ukraine Do I understand correctly
вы захватите всю Украину Я правильно
Temporarily Yes That is you you I understand
Временно Да То есть вы вы я так понимаю
that you see your victory that you should
что ты видишь свою победу что вы должны
seize Kyiv Lvov all of Ukraine Yes
захватить Киев Львов всю Украину Да
Yes Half
Да Наполовину
Cool Half - that's like
Прикольно Наполовину - это как
A
А
Kyiv Kharkov Odessa
Киев Харьков Одесса
Yeah So what will you do  with Kiev
Угу Так что вы будете делать с Киевом
Why do you need Kyiv They
Для чего вам Киев
won't give it back
Ничего отдадут его обратно
But only Russia Ukraine will not be an
Но только Россия Украина не будет
armed country at all It will not have
вооружжённой страной вообще У неё не
any weapons So wait I don't
будет оружия никакого Так подожди я не
understand Capture Kyiv to get it
понял Захватить Киев чтобы вернуть его
back I don't understand how to capture Kyiv
обратно Не понял как это захватить Киев
in order to disarm it
для того чтобы его разоворожить
Once what
Раз что
Disarm Once once
Разоворужить Разово разово
demilitarize Wait, say it in Russian
демилитаризировать Подожди по-русски
Once what Understood
скажи Разо что Понятно
Disarm Disarm Disarm Let's write it
Разовооружить
now
Разо разворожить Давай сейчас напишу
Let's write it because I don't understand this word
Давай напиши бо я не понимаю это слово
in Russian You write a
по-русски
long sentence I write one
Длинное предложение пишешь
word
Я одно слово пишу
Disturb It's taking so long And
Разворошить Так долго А
disarm Yeah Disarm And what does
разовооружить Ага Разовооружить А что
disarm mean
означает разовооружить
Well the meaning of this word I just didn't
Ну значение этого слова Я просто плохо
study Russian well at school And
русский учил в школе А
demilitarize
демилитаризировать
Demilitarize
Демилитаризировать
Hmm
Хм
cool Well demilitarize is in
прикольно Ну демилитаризировать - это по
Latin I already understand that If English is
латыне Это я уже понимаю Если английский
closer yes I just didn't quite understand uh in
ближе да я просто не совсем понял ээ в
Russian like once arm It's
русском языке как вот раз вооружить Это
arming is the opposite
вооружить - это наоборот
So speak in words you're fighting now I
Так говори словамираешься сейчас Я
just I just now understood yes what the
просто я я теперь только понял да что
word means
означает слово
demilitarization Demilitarization - this
демилитаризация Демилитаризация - это
means means disarmament That's it Yes yes yes
означает значит раза вооружение Вот так
exactly like that I got it I got it And
Да да да именно так Всё понял Понял А
why in Russian this word is
почему в русском языке это слово так и
called disarmament
называется разовооружение
In the sense of Why Well look well after all to arm,
В смысле Почему Ну смотриро
arm, arm -
ну ведь вооружи вооружить вооружить -
this is roughly speaking positive
это грубо говоря положительное
Disarm is negative And I
Разовооружить - это отрицательное А
got it That is the prefix disarm is the
понял То есть приставка разо - это
opposite yes it turns out in Russian That
наоборот да получается в русском языке
is to arm - this is to give weapons and
То есть вооружить - это э дать оружие а
disarm - this is to take weapons
разо вооружить - это забрать оружие Всё
Now I got it Yes Everything is correct I got it
теперь понял да Всё правильно Понял Всё
Now damn I understand what
теперь блин я понимаю что такое
demilitarization is Yes I got it Good And how do
демилитаризация Да понял Хорошо И как
you disarm Kyiv and leave
вот вы разовооружите Киев и уйдёте из
it
него
Yes So the Americans and Europeans will give it to him again They wo
Да Так американцы и европейцы снова ему
n't give it Why
Не дадут Почему
Yes because
Да потому что
Why Because they fear for themselves Ukraine will be a
Почему Потому что они за себя опасаются
neutral
У Украина - это будет нейтральная
territory where there are no weapons
территория на которой нет оружия
So if you leave Kyiv well I
Так если вы уйдёте из Киева
can't understand
не могу понять
what you don't understand
что вам непонятно
So look if you went to Kiev from Kyiv
Так смотри если вы зашли в Киево с Киева
to Kyiv disarmed Kyiv and then left
в Киев разоружили Киев а потом ушли из
Kyiv
Киева
So
Ну
what So in Kiev Kyiv will be given weapons again
и что Так в Кие Киеву снова дадут оружие
No, it will be a neutral territory
Нет это будет нейтральная территория у
that will have no weapons.
которой не будет оружия
It will be a country that has no weapons.
Это будет страна в которой нет оружия
It will simply be a buffer
Просто это будет территория буферная
zone. So what will stop the Europeans from
зона Так а что будет мешать европейцам
giving weapons to Kyiv again? There
снова дать оружие Киеву
will be war again, that's all. So why
Ну будет снова война вот и всё Так зачем
leave Kyiv then? It
тогда уходить из Киева
means the war will not stop.
Значит не будет прекращаться война
So how many of you Russians must die for you to
Так сколько вас россиян должно умереть
end this war? And
чтобы вы уже закончили эту войну А
how many of you Ukrainians must die? So
сколько вас украинцев должно умереть Так
look, we are on our own land, we have nowhere to
мы смотри мы на своей земле нам некуда
retreat. And Russia has a way to stop
отходить А России есть как остановить
this war. We simply have no choice. We have no
эту войну Просто у нас нет выбора У нас
choice. We cannot stop
нет выбора Мы не можем остановиться
because Russia will capture us and
потому что Россия захватит нас и всех
kill us all. We are not going to retreat anywhere. We are not going to attack. That's it.
убьёт Мы отходить никуда не собираемся
Look, yes. How many of you must die
так Смотри да Сколько вас должно умереть
for you to think that maybe we should not attack anymore. There will
чтобы вы подумали что может не надо уже
definitely be enough of you. How many of you
Ну вас точно хватит Ну сколько вас
should be able to. Well, what do you think? A million.
должно уметь Ну как ты считаешь Миллион
I say there will definitely be enough of you.
Я говорю вас точно хватит Ну для тебя
What is the limit for you? How many
какой предел Сколько для тебя погибших
Russians have died? That's already sad. There will
россиян Это уже печально
definitely be enough of you. Why are you
Вас точно хватит Ну почему ты
embarrassed to answer? That is, you are afraid to
стесняешься ответить То есть ты боишься
answer. Yes, that's not a respectable answer. I
ответить Да Это несолидный ответ В
mean, you are afraid to answer. I don't know the exact
смысле боишься ответить Я не знаю точную
number. You ask me such questions.  ask What is
цифру Вы мне такие вопросы задаёте Как
your name by the way
вас зовут кстати
Androniy
Андроний
Andrey Androniy I am Greek Yes, go ahead, in short
Андрей Андроний Я грек Да иди ты короче
You will be Andrey I am Greek My Greek
Ты будешь Андрей Я грек У меня греческое
name Androniy It is not Andrey It is like
имя Андроний Это не Андрей Это как
Artemy and Artyom are different names
Артемий и Артём разные имена
Okay My name will be Ivanidzo
Хорошо Меня будет звать Иванидзо
Ivanidzo Okay Ivanidzo you are
Иванидзо О'кей Иванидзо ты
Georgian Karvel
грузин Карвел
Why are you so nervous I am
Что ты так нервничаешь
not nervous at all You are nervous You are
Вообще не нервничаю Нервничаешь
never nervous How much Russian did you have
ни разу Сколько у тебя по-русскому языку
at school
в школе было
Positive assessment Got it Positive
Положительная оценка Понял Положительный
You had no negatives
У вас отрицательных не было
And how many do you have Positive - this is everything
А у тебя сколько Положительные - это всё
that is more than zero This is
что больше нуля Это и есть
positivity Probably also in the Soviet Union
положительность Ещё наверное в Советско
in the Soviet Union studies Yes yes yes And I was
в Советском Союзе учится Да да да И меня
taught in the Soviet Union that the word
учили в Советском Союзе что слово
disarmament is written
разовооружение пишется
disarmament and not disarmament
разоружение а не разовооружение
You wrote at once
Ты написал разом
arm and speak specifically
вооружи и говори специально
asked again That is, you even Well, okay,
переспрашивал То есть ты даже Ну ладно
sorry Look, do I understand correctly that you do not
извини Смотри я правильно понимаю что ты
even know your Russian language and are
не знаешь свой даже русский язык и
climbing to say something about
лезете что-то там говорить про
Russian-speakers in Ukraine yes
русскоязычных в Украине да
Come on  What did you
Давай Что ты
write You wrote one-time disarming
написал Ты написал разово разоворежие
Disarming I
Разовоожение
hear you testing my knowledge of the Russian
Слышен ты что меня на знание русского
language Write this
языка проверяешь Напиши правильно это
word correctly Definitely better than you Well, look,
слово Точно лучше чем ты Ну смотри
write the correct word You wrote
напиши правильное слово Ты написал
disarming disarming
разовооружить
disarming Well, how how to
разовоурежие разовооружение Ну как как
write correctly Come on
правильно написать Давай
How is the word disarming written correctly
Как правильно слово разоружение пишется
Well, here's the last one
Ну вот последнее
Read the last one How does it sound
Прочитай последнее Как оно звучит
Disarming One-time
Разовоуружение
What
Разово Что
Read it yourself Well, you've already written one-time Come on write the
Прочитай сам Ну у тебя написано разово
next version Yes, go
Давай следующей версии пиши
Write come on We we will learn the word
Да иди Напиши давай Мы мы выучим слово Я
We will find how to do it
хороший учитель Мы найдём как её
correctly Teacher if you if
правильно Учитель если ты если у
your students can't write it the third time,
тебя ученики с третьего раза написать не
but then they remember Come on, you'll
могут а зато потом помнят Давай с
write it the sixth time Come on, you'll
шестого напишешь Давай
write it Correctly Let me
давай ты напишешь Правильно Давай я
say the word and you just
скажу слово а ты просто фонетически
listen to it phonetically and write it in letters Two
послушаешь его и напишешь буквами Два
Disarming Listen, what are
Разоружение
you just to one letter Well,
Слушай что ты просто до одной буквы Ну
write the word disarming Write
напиши слово разоружение Напиши вот
just as you hear disarming
просто как слышишь разоружение
You, you wrote disarming
Ты ты написал разоружение
What's wrong  Come on, listen again
А что неправильно Давай ещё раз слушай
Come on, listen carefully
Давай фанечески внимательно слушай
Disarmament, you wrote to spread out,
Разоружение ты написал разокинуться
impudent, need to throw yourself in You wrote
нагальной треба вкинуться Ты написал
disarmament No, come on, listen carefully
разоружений Нет давай слушай внимательно
This is a verbal dictation, such a
Это вот словесный диктант такой
funetic dictation I say disarmament Come on,
фанеческий диктант Я говорю разоружение
disarmament Write this word Well, you
Давай разоружение Напиши это слово Ну ты
made four attempts The sixth one we will
четыре попытки делал Шестой у нас
get is disarmament
получится
I seriously want that Well, come on Okay That's it
разоружение Я серьёзно хочу чтобы Ну
Hallelujah Read, read how it
Аллилуйя Читай
sounds Well, read how what you
звучит Ну прочитай как звучит то что
wrote sounds You wrote it correctly As you
написал Ты правильно написал Как ты
said, so I wrote it Correctly Here it is,
сказал так я и написал Правильно Вот оно
disarmament Now, just read
разоружение Вот прочитай просто ты ещё
it again to remember
раз это чтобы запомнить
You think I don't know the Russian language I don't think you
Ты думаешь я русский язык язык не знаю
know Come on How many cases are there in the Russian
знаешь Давай Сколько падежей в русском
language
языке
Six Name it
Шесть Назови
Modifying genitive
Изменительный родительный
dative Wait
дательный Подожди
nominative genitive accusative
именительный родительный винительный
dative instrumental prepositional
дательный творительный предложный
mixed up in places Come on again
местами перепутал Давай ещё раз
Well, you name it so that no let's in places in
Ну ты назови чтобы нет давай местами
places you changed several Come on
местами ты поменял несколько Давай ещё
again Nominative genitive Correct And
раз Именительный родительный Правильно А
then
дальше
let's
давай
Nominative  genitive
Именительный родительный
accusative dative
винительный
instrumental prepositional
дательный творительный предложный Да
What's the difference [ __ ] Okay, let it be
какая разница бляд Ладно пусть будет
OK How many letters are in the Russian alphabet
О'кей Сколько букв в русском алфавите
33 That's right Listen, well done The
33 Правильно Слушай молодец За первый
movement is going on for the first grade Okay And now the question In the
класс движ идёт Хорошо А теперь вопрос В
Russian language, come on One poker, two
русском языке давай Одна кочерга две
pokers, three pokers Doesn't hang
кочерги три кочер Не
The Russian-speaker will hang Hangs
зависает Зависнет русскоязычник
up And that's how they are all for the Russian
Развиснее А вот так они все за русский
language in Ukraine That's it And here the word
язык в Украине Всё А тут слово
disarmament was written on the sixth try On the
разоружение написа с шестого раза С
sixth try to write the word
шестого раза написать слово
disarmament Disarmament is what hasn't
разоружение Разовооружение это что
happened Like subscribe comment
только не было Лайк подписка комент
Subscribe to Telegram right now Here's the
Подпишись на й Telegram прям зараз Ось
deal And the
вн А
priest is very and very important YouTube is
попик це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube
driving us through the card into a shadow ban
заганяе нас через каргеор в тіньовий бан
and a lot of videos are not shown to people
и дуже багато відео не показуется людям
Information about streams is sometimes not shown
вчасно не показуется інформація про
so that we have a quick
стрими для того щоб ми мали оперативний
connection subscribe  straight away and the pop is
зв'язок підпишиться прям зараз а попик
there in the telegram okmdeo there is also useful and
там в телеграмі окмдео ще теж є цікава и
useful information and we are obliged to you to
корисна інформація и мы повин з вами
keep up with constant operational communications
тримати постійний оператив зв'язок
Regardless of that, I will show you about this
Незалежно від того чи покаже вам про цей
YouTube Glory to Ukraine Subscribe
YouTube Слава Україні Підпишись